

Morenike Oyewole

I'm a knowledgeable Frontend developer adept for creating user-friendly websites that meets clients need. I'am also an experienced Pianist and music teacher with vast experience in the music industry. I'm from Oyo state and I am currently based in Lagos, Nigeria.

Hobbies/Interests:

Surfing, online shopping, coding, playing piano, teaching

└+2348099772916 ☑herroyalpianist@gmail.com

in

(O



Skills

Professional Skills
HTML
CSS
Javascript
JQuery
React
Web design

Soft Skills
Effective communication
Team work
Time management
Interpersonal skills
Fast learner
Attention to details

Work Experience

Manifield Manpower Consultancy / Assistant Technical Officer

Mar, 2021 - PRESENT. Lagos, Nigeria

 Cooperated with the senior Chief technology officer to align management of junior staff with business priorities and goals.

Freelancer / Pianist

Jan, 2016 - PRESENT. Lagos, Nigeria

- Formed and played piano for an All Female band (Bandittude).
- Performed with several artists including Rudeboy, Eva,

- Performed hands-on work (building and developing) on technologies such as wordpress, Podio and click-up
- Served as Information Technology (IT) advisor to HRs
- Coordinated with management teams to plan, develop, align and execute strategies that would meet client's vision, mission and purpose.

Muna, Yinka Davis at different functions in and out of the country.

HOME Music School / Music Teacher

Jan, 2015- PRESENT, Lagos, Nigeria

- Taught private music lessons to students including (special needs).
- · Prepared students for live performances and ABRSM (UK) practical and theory exams.
- · Developed strong working relationships with teachers, parents and students to propel school and departmental vision and goals.

Trainee / Front-end developer

Jun, 2020 - PRESENT, Lagos, Nigeria

- Maintain and improve website.
- · Develop user-friendly and responsive web pages using markup languages like HTML, CSS and Javascript

Education and Couses

Yaba College Of Technology / National Diploma

Grade V Music Theory

Sep, 2012 - Feb, 2015, Yaba, Lagos Nigeria Nov, 2015 - Nov, 2016, Lagos, Nigeria

Musical Society Of Nigeria (MUSON) / Associated Board of the Royal Schools of Music (ABRSM UK) / Grade V Piano

Jul 2018- Jul, 2019, Lagos, Nigeria

Front-end development course -Udemy

Jul 2020 - Sept. 2020

Responsive Web Design -Freecodecamp

Feb 2021 - Present

Becoming a better Music teacher -Futurelearn

Mar 2021 - Present

References

Available on request